<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our clients on CodeScouts</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/</link><description>Recent content in Our clients on CodeScouts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Axa Assistance</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/axa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/axa/</guid><description>AXA Assistance is a multinational specialized in providing assistance services, with over 50 years of experience in the Spanish market.</description></item><item><title>BeWorkLive</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/beworklive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/beworklive/</guid><description>BeWorkLive is a consulting and training company specialized in the camping sector. At BeWorkLive they design, develop and adapt customized courses in different pedagogical formats, in-person, virtual classroom and online.</description></item><item><title>Inno-IT</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/inno-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/inno-it/</guid><description>We dedicate ourselves above all to the management of IT races.We have been participating in the digital transformation of leading companies of all branches of activity at national and international levels for more than six years.</description></item><item><title>K-lagan</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/k-lagan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/k-lagan/</guid><description>K-LAGAN is a strategic technology services consultancy, where the focus is on people, committed to their team and always at the forefront of the latest technological trends.</description></item><item><title>Mirai</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/mirai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/mirai/</guid><description>Mirai is a hotelier partner in the common objective of bringing direct sale, its commercial independence, the reduction of distribution costs and access without intermediaries to the largest number of potential guests, always within the general framework that these actionsThey contribute to increase the benefits of the hotel.</description></item><item><title>Movicoders</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/movicoders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/movicoders/</guid><description>Movicoders implements management, traceability, automation, and integration solutions through a close and highly skilled and motivated human team.</description></item><item><title>Nectios</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/nectios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/nectios/</guid><description>A platform that allows you to transform your event space into a profitable long-term community with just one click, but you choose where to start.</description></item><item><title>Submer</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/submer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/submer/</guid><description>We enable next-generation cooling and automation for data &amp;amp; energy-intense environments by integrating our pristine, highly-efficient &amp;amp; sustainable technologies. We are solving the challenges of today and powering the use cases of the future.</description></item><item><title>Wallion</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/wallion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/clients/wallion/</guid><description>In Wallion we develop custom-made software to offer personalised solutions for companies that want digital transformation. We are digital sherpas.</description></item></channel></rss>