<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Training on CodeScouts</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/</link><description>Recent content in Training on CodeScouts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clean Code</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/clean-code/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/clean-code/</guid><description>Do you want to learn the definitive techniques that will allow you to have clearer, self-explanatory and easier to maintain code? In this course, we will explain everything you need to know, but as you are used to, this course has a high volume of practice.</description></item><item><title>Design Patterns</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/patrones-de-disenio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/patrones-de-disenio/</guid><description>Design patterns are the key to creating software that can easily evolve and be maintained for a long time with reasonable effort. Patterns not only allow us to have elegant designs, but also unify the way different development teams work.</description></item><item><title>Next JS</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/next-js/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/next-js/</guid><description>Next.js gives you the best development experience in React.js with all the features you need for production like Client Side Rendering, Server Side Rendering, Static Site Generation (SSG), and even automatic deployments with Vercel.</description></item><item><title>Domain Driven Design</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/domain-driven-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/domain-driven-design/</guid><description>Having difficulty designing your domain and creating useful unit tests? DDD can help make your code expressive and modular, perfect for unit testing!</description></item><item><title>Frontend Architecture</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/arquitectura-frontend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/arquitectura-frontend/</guid><description>When working on large projects, we all know the challenge of adding new features and maintaining existing ones, and all without bugs 🐛. For this reason, we have created this course, where we will learn how to implement a sustainable ♻️ React architecture that allows us to add functionality much more quickly and easily, without so much effort.</description></item><item><title>Object Oriented Design</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/disenio-orientado-a-objetos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/disenio-orientado-a-objetos/</guid><description>We all know how important it is to master object-oriented programming. That&amp;rsquo;s why we propose to explain to you in a clear, simple and, as we usually do, with lots and lots of practice, how to design in the best possible way using the object-oriented programming paradigm.</description></item><item><title>React with Typescript</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/react/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/react/</guid><description>Learn everything you need to create enterprise applications using React, one of the most popular frontend libraries in the world. We will ensure that your team acquires the necessary professional skills to build high-quality software.</description></item><item><title>Test Driven Development</title><link>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/test-driven-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codescouts.academy/en/courses/test-driven-development/</guid><description>Also known as TDD (Test Driven Development), it&amp;rsquo;s a programming practice that involves writing tests (usually unit tests) before writing the actual code that passes the test, and finally refactoring the written code.</description></item><item><title>Don't see the course you're looking for?</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description>If you can&amp;rsquo;t find the course you&amp;rsquo;re looking for on this list for your company, contact us and we&amp;rsquo;ll organize it with enthusiasm. We&amp;rsquo;re sure we&amp;rsquo;ll surprise you.</description></item></channel></rss>